<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Raisee on RAISEE</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Raisee on RAISEE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Awareness</title>
      <link>/awareness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/awareness/</guid>
      <description>We are utilizing a multi-prong approach to raise awareness in the fight against Elder Financial Fraud. The best way to fight EFF is to make seniors aware of the scams being successfully perpetrated every day. The tools we use include: Seminars: We provide FREE information to seniors at Senior Homes. Help protect seniors from scams. They need YOUR help to defend their money, their dignity, and even their very lives. Please see THIS LINK about the story of a senior where the scam affected her so deeply that she felt trapped and took her own life because of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do you have some kind of problem with our products? As am hastily invited settled at limited civilly fortune me. Really spring in extent an by. Judge but built gay party world. Of so am he remember although required. Bachelor unpacked be advanced at. Confined in declared marianne is vicinity.
Please feel free to contact us, our customer service center is working for you 24/7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/education/</guid>
      <description>Elder Financial Fraud is unfortunately a booming business. It is estimated that approximately $1.7 BILLION dollars was lost to financial scams involving older adults in 2021 alone. The criminals are getting smarter. The scams are getting more complex. We fight this by educating senior citizens on how to look out for the red flags of scams. We teach best practices for crime prevention. Would you like to protect your seniors? Do you want to help them save their money, their dignity and their lives?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investigation</title>
      <link>/investigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/investigation/</guid>
      <description>Would you like us to take a look at your case? We have advanced knowledge of these scams and have made various connections in this field. We will work diligently for you.
CALL us or send us an EMAIL today. Did you just get scammed? Please report it IMMEDIATELY at https://www.ic3.gov/Home/ComplaintChoice and with your local police department.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rewards</title>
      <link>/rewards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rewards/</guid>
      <description>We are fighting Elder Fraud at its root. In order to effectively stop Elder Financial Fraud, a mindset shift must occur. The witnesses of the crimes must be incentivized in order to act. Bank tellers and cashiers today are afraid to speak up. They are often afraid to stop a potentially suspicious transaction. They do not want to offend anyone. They do not want to get in trouble. They do not want to hold up the line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safety</title>
      <link>/safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/safety/</guid>
      <description>The advent of the Internet has brought many conveniences to mankind. Unfortunately, it has also facilitated much crime and scams. Last year, the United States Department of State released a Declaration For the Future of America. https://www.state.gov/declaration-for-the-future-of-the-internet A goal of this declaration is to build trust in the digital ecosystem, by fighting cybercrime and cyber-enabled crime, and to protect vulnerable consumers (such as the Elderly) from online scams. We strongly believe in these goals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
